Good Morning
Good morning, Perrin.
Good morning, this is Perorin.
I'm in Sendai.
Today is the ending tour of Denpa Gumi Ink in Sendai Park.
I'm here in Sendai.
This is the building district of Sendai.
I'm going to visit various areas for the ending tour starting today.
It was a lot of fun!
I'm looking forward to it!
We had the Tokyo show the other day.
We had guests at the Tokyo show.
so this Sendai show is the first time for us to do it with just the members.
This show in Sendai is the first time for me to perform with just the members.
so the setlist will be totally different.
We played some songs for the first time and some for the first time in a while.
and some songs we haven't played in a while
I'm a little nervous.
I'm going to rehearse well and
I'm going to enjoy the show.
I'm looking forward to it!
Oh, no, no, no, no!
It was auto-locked.
I was locked out.
I'm glad I have my cell phone.
We've been in Sendai since the beginning.
Here's today's catering!
What a hot soup!
I wonder if it's a Sendai specialty or something.
Let's open it!
Open it!
Ta-da-da!
Looks delicious!
Delicious!
There's pork, taro, deep-fried tofu, leeks, and all sorts of other things in there!
I'm so happy to have something hot at a live concert like this!
I'll have a bowl of this and eat it, too!
The soup has a nice fatty pork flavor.
Bon appétit!
Hot, hot, hot!
So delicious!
Soy sauce base
The pork fat is great for thirst quenching!
I had my lunch well before rehearsal!
The warm soup makes you more appetizing!
A fan from Tohoku has compiled the history of our consecutive trips to Tohoku!
This is how they put it all together!
The illustrations are super cute!
The fans in Tohoku are so warm!
Good night!
Now we are going to the venue for rehearsal!
The venue? To the stage
I'm going to the stage.
Oh, yes. Excuse me.
Please.
Big cloth
Today's venue is here.
We practiced a lot of songs we haven't played in a while.
We need luggage.
Luggage?
Come back when we're in the hall.
I'll bring a lip gloss.
Yeah!
You want me to put it in?
Yes, sir.
Shall we?
Slowly.
He's so cute.
He's so cute!
You scared the shit out of me.
I was so surprised how close the camera was.
It was as close as a microscope.
Specifically.
What's a microscope?
It's a microscope that allows you to see into the microscopic world.
I'm a science guy.
It's kinda cool.
Yes, sir.
Here you go.
Well, good luck on your national tour!
With songs that are not dense and careful.
See you there!
Best regards, everyone!
Live show is over!
The show is over!
This is the first show of the tour around Sendai Park.
I'm glad everyone enjoyed the show.
There were a lot of rare faces wearing egg-colored penlights.
They usually support us on social networking sites and so on.
I thought that there were many people who support us through social media and finally came to the site today.
I also got a lot of power from them.
It was so much fun!
The air is so good!
Is this the air of Sendai?
I can smell the beef tongue!
It really smells like beef tongue or grilled fish.
It smells like beef tongue or grilled fish.
We're going to go around the ending tour from now on.
Today was the last time to go to Sendai and Tohoku.
I haven't been able to go often, but I was so happy to be able to go on the last leg of the tour!
In the backstage, there was a paper with all the information about the events that have been held here and there.
I thought that the fans in Sendai and Tohoku were waiting for us because they loved us so much.
I'm so happy!
That's why I had such a good time in Sendai!
Thank you so much!
Next stop is Taiwan!
I'm quitting Nikko and going abroad suddenly!
It's been a long time since I've been to Taiwan.
It's been 7 years and 8 years since I was in Bepo.
I think it's been 7 or 8 years since I've been there.
I'm glad to be able to go there by airwaves
I wonder if people from back then will come.
Well then...
Thank you very much.
I'm going to have a special meeting and then go home.
On the shinkansen on the way home, I had a gyutan bento.
Beef tongue is the most popular food in Sendai, isn't it?
Sendai's beef tongue is very tender.
It was very tender, but it was crispy and satisfying.
It was super delicious!
When you go on a national tour
It's so fascinating to be able to eat delicious food from all over the country!
But since this is the last tour, I want to leave as many memories as possible with the Peroline Tube, so I'm going to tour with my memories.